let Questions = [{
        question: "Choose the correct answers from the below?",
        choices: ["A. Javascript is an extension of the Java programming language",
            "B. Javascript is a scripting language but not an object-oriented language",
            "C. Javascript is used for manipulating the DOM(Document Object Model) elements of the HTML WebPage",
            "D. Javascript is used for form validation only on client-side web applications and it cannot be used on server side"
        ],
        answer: "C. Javascript is used for manipulating the DOM(Document Object Model) elements of the HTML WebPage"
    },

    {
        question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
        choices: ["A. Alternative to if-else",
            "B. Switch statement",
            "C. If-then-else statement",
            "D. immediate if"
        ],
        answer: "D. immediate if"
    }

    ,

    {
        question: " Javascript is _ language?",
        choices: ["Dynamic computer programming language",
            "Javascript is an object-oriented programming language",
            "Javascript is a Scripting language",
            "All the Above"
        ],
        answer: "All the Above"

    }

    ,
    {
        question: "what is the correct file extension for Javascript files?",
        choices: ["A. Java",
            "B. Javascript",
            "C. Js",
            "D. script"
        ],
        answer: "C. Js"
    }

    ,

    {
        question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display “Topzenith.com” in an alert box using JavaScript?",
        choices: ["A. alertbox(“topzenith.com”);",
            "B. msgbox(“Topzenith.com”);",
            "C. alert(“Topzenith.com”);",
            "D. msg(“topzenith.com”);"
        ],
        answer: "C. alert(“Topzenith.com”);"
    }

    ,

    {
        question: "typeof null",
        choices: ["null", "undefined", "object", "number"],
        answer: "object"
    }

    ,

    {
        question: "What is the output of below? 33 == 33.0",
        choices: ["A. true",
            "B. 33",
            "C. false",
            "D. none of the above"
        ],
        answer: "A. true"
    }

    ,

    {
        question: "JavaScript is ________ language?",
        choices: ["A. an interpreted",
            "B. a compiled",
            "C. Translated",
            "D. None of the above"
        ],
        answer: "A. an interpreted"
    }

    ,

    {
        question: "What will this code print? >>>  a=10 >>>  alert(a+10)",
        choices: ["A. This code will raise an exception",
            "B. a+10",
            "C. None of these",
            "D. 20"
        ],
        answer: "D. 20"
    }

    ,

    {
        question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display “GeeksforGeeks” in an alert box using JavaScript?",
        choices: ["A. alertbox(“GeeksforGeeks”);",
            "B. msg(“GeeksforGeeks”);",
            "C. msgbox(“GeeksforGeeks”);",
            "D. alert(“GeeksforGeeks”);"
        ],
        answer: "D. alert(“GeeksforGeeks”);"
    }


]